Guide to the C. Lyn Fox Papers pertaining to the Longshoremen's strike and the Pacific Coast maritime strike, 1934 -1937
Department of Special Collections
C. Lyn Fox Papers pertaining to the Longshoremen's strike and the Pacific Coast maritime strike,
1934 -1937
Special Collections M769
Fox, C. Lyn
2.5 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions:
None.
Provenance:
Gift of Jean F. George, 1995
BIOGRAPHY
C. Lyn Fox was assistant to Thomas G. Plant, the President of the Waterfront Employer's Union, and wrote news memoranda for the president, 1935-1936.
CONTAINER LIST
- Agreements between the Steamship Companies and all seven Unions. (International Longshoremen's Association, Sailors Union, Firemen, etc. Association, Radio Telegraphists Association, National Organization of Masters, Mates and Pilots of America, Marine Engineers Beneficial Association) [Feb. 1937] (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Agreements between the Steamship Companies and all seven Unions. [Feb. 1937], (Xeroxes) (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Daily Memorandums to Mr. Plant (President of the Waterfront Employer's Union). [1935] (Box 1, Folder 3)
- News Memorandum, vol.2. [1936] (Box 1, Folder 4)
- News Memorandum, vol.3. [1936] (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Index: News Memoranda [1936] (Box 1, Folder 6)
- San Francisco Bay District. Hours worked by Longshoremen assigned to Gangs and their earnings. From April 1, 1935. (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Statement from the Waterfront Employers Union on the Strike. [1934] (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Arbitration before the National Longshoremen's Board (Employers) [1934] (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Strike Arbitration. [1935-36] (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, Telegrams, Memoranda. [1935-37] (Box 2, Folder 4)
- "Speech Folder". [1935-37] (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Addresses and other material concerning the strike; printed material. [1935-37] (Box 2, Folder 6)
- San Francisco Chamber of Commerce: News-Letter. [Sept.1935 -Nov. 1936] (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Waterfront Employers Bulletin. [1936/37] (Box 2, Folder 8)
- "Ships in various Ports." [1936/37] (Box 2, Folder 9)
- An Address by Thomas G. Plant (President of the Waterfront Employer's Union). [1937] (Box 2, Folder 10)
- American Steamship Owners' Association: Bulletin. [1937] (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Waterfront Employers Association of Southern California: Bulletins. [1937] (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Labour Agreement between the Longshoremen Union and the Shipowners. [1937] (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Labour Agreements with the Steamship Companies. [1937] (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Labour Agreements with the Steamship Companies. [1937] (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Labour Agreements with the Steamship Companies. [1937] (Box 2, Folder 16)
- US Maritime Commission: Bulletin. [March 1937] (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Loyal Legion of Loggers and Lumbermen. [1937] (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Anti-Communist Bulletin. [March 1937] (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Printed Material (Misc.) (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Printed Material (Misc.) (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Handbook on Information on Awards and Agreements: Longshore and Port Crafts. Adjustments of Disputes with Port Labor on the Pacific Coast in 1934-1935. Volume I. Longshore. (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Handbook of Information on Awards and Agreements: Volume IV. Seafaring Labor - US Pacific Coast. (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Law and Order in San Francisco. A Beginning. Submitted by the San Francisco Chamber of Commerce. [1916] (Box 4, Folder 1)
- The Waterfront and General Strikes San Francisco, 1934. A Brief History by Paul Eliel. [1934] (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Quarterly Report on the Employment of American Steam and Motor Merchant Vessels of 1,000 Gross Tons and over as of December 31, 1936. (Box 4, Folder 2)
- "What is the Shipping Federation?" Reprinted from Harbour and Shipping [1936?] (Box 4, Folder 3)
- The San Francisco Examiner December 9, 1936;Article on the strike. (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Newsletter and Wasp [September 26, 1936; October 31, 1936] (Box 4, Folder 5)